Saidnabi Yuldashkhadjaev

.NET Developer

♥ Tashkent. Uzbekistan

PROFILE

I enjoy working as a developer! I have worked on .NET apps for almost a year and learned a lot. My main goal is to make apps that are easy for people to use and fun too. I'm really good at making web apps using ASP.NET. I'm also good at fixing problems and making apps better. I always want to learn more and get even better at what I do to make great apps.

SKILLS

SOFT SKILLS Communication, Problem-Solving, Time management, Attention

todetail, Teamwork, Continuous learning, Critical thinking, Networking,

Creativity

HARD SKILLS C#, ASP.NET Core Web API, ASP.NET MVC, Entity Framework Core,

Information System Engineering

MSSQL Server, PostgreSQL, SQLServer, LINQ, REST, GraphQL, XUnit,

Design Principles and Patterns.

EDUCATION

Kimyo International **University in Tashkent**

September 2019 - May 2023

Najot Ta'lim

July 2022 - May 2023

.NET (Bootcamp)

I learned C# and web API development at Najot Ta'lim, focusing on RESTful services, HTTP, and security measures like JWT and OAuth2. Excited to apply these skills in the future.

University experience built my programming foundation, teaching

essential skills for software development career.

Mohirdey

December 2022 - April 2023

.NET (Online private course)

Learned .NET and C# programming languages, Completed coursework in web API development, focusing on RESTful services, HTTP, and security measures like JWT and OAuth2.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Food - Market

2019 - 2021

Sales Manager

Product sales, marketing

Sareed

2022 - Now

.NET Developer

Web application development

ACTIVITIES

Sharpist - 2022

2022 - NOW

Volunteer

Microsoft Developers Community in Uzbekistan

CERTIFICATIONS

2023 - HackerRank C# (Basic) - Credential ID: E054340883FE

2023 - HackerRank Problem Solving (Basic) - Credential ID: B87AFD151505

2023 - HackerRank Problem Solving (Intermediate) - Credential ID: 8586CDD70114

PROJECTS

Kassa-Uz **Team project**

Kassa-Uz is an open-source point-of-sale (POS) system designedformarkets. It provides an easy-to-use interface for

managingsales, inventory, and customer information. My role is key

developer

Fleet - Flow **Team project**

I worked as a .NET developer on the challenging FleetFlow

project. Mymain task was to develop and maintain the REST API using

thelatesttechnologies. I also focused on writing clear

documentationandproviding support to the team. This experience helped megainexpertise in .NET Core, C#, and REST API development.

LANGUAGES

Uzbek - Native/Bilingual English - Pre Intermediate Russian - Elementary